{
    "question": "Because he is appointed te be the director of the cempang\u200b",
    "attachments": [],
    "answers": [
        {
            "answer": "<p><strong>Jawaban:</strong></p><p>tanya ke guru semoga membantu</p>",
            "attachments": []
        },
        {
            "answer": "<p><strong>Jawaban:</strong></p><p>yyyyyyyyyyyyy</p><p><strong>Penjelasan:</strong></p><p>y6yyyyyyyyy</p>",
            "attachments": []
        }
    ],
    "related_questions": [
        {
            "slug": "you-an-old-table-533",
            "question": "You....... an old table\u200b",
            "attachments": [],
            "answers": [
                {
                    "answer": "<p><strong>Jawaban:</strong></p><p>You....... an old table\u200b</p><p>You <strong>have </strong>an old table.</p><p></p><p><strong>Penjelasan:</strong></p><p>Jawaban pada kalimat di atas dicetak tebal dan merupakan bentuk Simple Present Tense karena menjelaskan fakta. Jika subjek nya adalah kata You, maka harus memakai kata kerja Have yang artinya memiliki.</p><p>Semoga membantu ya.</p>",
                    "attachments": []
                }
            ]
        },
        {
            "slug": "buatlah-tentang-benda-binatang-orang-atau-tempat-participant-679",
            "question": "Buatlah tentang benda, binatang, orang atau tempat ( participant secara umum)    Lebih disukai yg terkait dengan teknologi. \r\nKalau yg dibicarakan benda lebih menyoroti fungsi benda tsb. (yang pembuatannya merujuk dengan Report text)\r\n\r\n\u25a1Bhs.inggris\u25a1\u200b",
            "attachments": [],
            "answers": [
                {
                    "answer": "<p><strong>Jawaban:</strong></p><p>I have a smartphone. It is one of many sophisticated things that I&#039;ve ever had. I use my smartphone to communicate with my family and friends. I don&#039;t have any game apps in my smartphone because I don&#039;t like to play games with my smartphone. I just like to watch youtube videos and tik tok videos on my smartphone. I also use my smartphone to communicate with google assistant. I enjoy communicating with that artificial intelligence because it&#039;s really cool! I can also practice speaking English with my google assistant. I feel happy to have my smartphone. Thank you.</p><p></p><p><strong>Penjelasan:</strong></p><p>Aku memiliki sebuah telepon pintar. Telpon pintarku adalah salah satu dari banyak hal canggih yang pernah kumiliki. Aku menggunakan smartphoneku untuk berkomunikasi dengan keluarga dan teman-temanku. Aku tidak memiliki aplikasi game di smartphoneku karena aku tidak suka bermain game dengan smartphoneku. Aku hanya suka menonton video youtube dan video tik tok di smartphoneku. Aku juga menggunakan smartphoneku untuk berkomunikasi dengan google asisten. Aku senang berkomunikasi dengan kecerdasan buatan tersebut karena sangat keren! Aku juga bisa berlatih berbicara bahasa Inggris dengan google asistenku. Aku merasa senang memiliki smartphoneku. Terima kasih.</p><p>Semoga membantu ya.</p>",
                    "attachments": []
                }
            ]
        },
        {
            "slug": "1-eric-is-a-german-engineerhe-comes-from-a-france-c-frenc-443",
            "question": "1. Eric is a German engineer.He comes from....    a. France c. French e. German\r\n\r\nb. Germany d. Switzerland \r\n\r\n2. Peter is a foreign student, he comes from \r\n\r\nAustralia.He speaks.....\r\n\r\na. Australia c. Germany e. British\r\n\r\nb. England d. English\r\n\r\n3. X : How is your mother today ?\r\n\r\nY : .......\r\n\r\na. I am fine,thanks d. He is not Fine\r\n\r\nb. She is fine ,thanks e. He is fine, thanks\r\n\r\nc. He is not fine\r\n\r\n4. Miss . Chang comes from china.What is her \r\n\r\nnationality?\r\n\r\na. Chinese c. Japanese e. Italy\r\n\r\nb. Korea d. French\r\n\r\n5. A : .....?\r\n\r\nB : British.\r\n\r\na. What\u2019s your address? \r\n\r\nb. What\u2019s your job?\r\n\r\nc. What\u2019s your country? \r\n\r\nd. What\u2019s your hobby?\r\n\r\ne. What\u2019s your Nationality?\r\n\r\n6. Yani : ....,madam? My name is Yani.\r\n\r\nMrs. Asti : How do you do? I am Mrs. Asti.\r\n\r\na. Nice to meet you d. How are you\r\n\r\nb. How do you do e. Fine,thank you\r\n\r\nc. May I introduce\r\n\r\n7. Mrs. Astuti comes f rom United State. She \r\n\r\nspeaks.....\r\n\r\na. America c. American e. Dutch\r\n\r\nb. England d. spanish\r\n\r\nHello, I\u2019m Silvana ,I\u2019m Italian.I\u2019m from \r\n\r\nItaly.This is my class at the tower language \r\n\r\nschool.It\u2019s a small class but it\u2019s nice. The \r\n\r\nstudents aren\u2019t all from italy ; they are from \r\n\r\nspain , France , Germany and Japan, too. My \r\n\r\nfriend sabine is French , she is from Paris , she \r\n\r\nis a new student , but her english is very good. \r\n\r\nMr. Levis is our teacher , he\u2019s from Manchester. \r\n\r\nHe\u2019s very nice and polite. He\u2019s a good teacher.\r\n\r\n8. X : Where is Silvana from?\r\n\r\nY Oh, she comes from.....\r\n\r\na. Spain c. Italy e. France\r\n\r\nb. England d. Germany\r\n\r\n9. X : Who is Silvana\u2019s Teacher ?\r\n\r\nY : Her teacher is......\r\n\r\na. Mrs. Sabine c. Mr. Levis e. Mr. Sabine\r\n\r\nb. My friend d. Mrs. Levis\r\n\r\n10. X : Where does study now?\r\n\r\nY : She Studies at.....\r\n\r\na. Tower mechanic school\r\n\r\nb. Tower school of design\r\n\r\nc. Tower stylist school\r\n\r\nd. Tower language school\r\n\r\ne. Tower gymnastic school\r\n\r\n11. Tom : How do you do,Joko?\r\n\r\nJoko : How do you do ? I am very happy \r\n\r\n....you\r\n\r\na. Meet c. to meeting e. to meet\r\n\r\nb. Meeting d. met\r\n\r\n12. A : ...... my name is Toni.I am the first year of\r\n\r\n SMK.\r\n\r\nB : I am Rudi. How do you do, Toni ?\r\n\r\na. How do you do ? \r\n\r\nb. How is Toni\r\n\r\nc. May I introduce myself?\r\n\r\nd. What can I do you for you\r\n\r\ne. I would like to introduce you to Toni\r\n\r\n13. Nany : Hello, I\u2019m Nany.\r\n\r\nNindy : Hi, I\u2019m Nindy.\r\n\r\nNany : .........\r\n\r\nNindy : I live on Jln. Jenderal Sudirman.\r\n\r\na. How do you do? d. How is Toni?\r\n\r\nb. Where do you live? e. How are you?\r\n\r\nc. Where are you ?\r\n\r\n14. Aldo : Good morning , Mr. Sandra.\r\n\r\nMr. Sandra : Good Morning , Aldo . How are\r\n\r\n You?\r\n\r\nAldo : I\u2019m fine. Thank you.\r\n\r\nThe underlined greeting above tells us that Aldo \r\n\r\nmet Mr. Sandra.....\r\n\r\na. At about eight p.m. d. in the evening\r\n\r\nb. In the afternoon e. at night\r\n\r\nc. At about seven a.m.\r\n\r\n15. Iwan is my best friend, I like ....very much.\r\n\r\na. Him b. His c. he d. she e. we\r\n\r\n16. 1. X : Ok, see you later\r\n\r\n2. Y : I\u2019m going to visit my grandfather.\r\n\r\n3. Y : Good Afternoon.\r\n\r\n4. X : Hi, Good afternoon.\r\n\r\n5. X : Where are you going?\r\n\r\na. 4 \u2013 3 \u2013 2 \u2013 5 \u2013 1 \r\n\r\nb. 4 \u2013 3 \u2013 2 \u2013 1 \u2013 5 \r\n\r\nc. 4 \u2013 3 \u2013 5 \u2013 2 \u2013 1\r\n\r\nd. 4 \u2013 3 \u2013 5 \u2013 1 \u2013 2\r\n\r\ne. 4 \u2013 3 \u2013 1 \u2013 2 \u2013 5\r\n\r\n17. If you given some aids. You say thank for.....\r\n\r\na. Giving c. coming e. asking\r\n\r\nb. Helping d. kidding\r\n\r\n18. These are expression for thanking, except....\r\n\r\na. Thank you d. many thanks\r\n\r\nb. Thanks so much e. not at all\r\n\r\nc. It\u2019s very kind of you\r\n\r\n19. Dina : ...... I come very late today.\r\n\r\nManager : It doesn\u2019t matter , please go to work.\r\n\r\na. Thank you c. I am sorry e. Ok\r\n\r\nb. I am happy d. do you know?\r\n\r\n20. Mrs. Aryani......my teacher. She always....early \r\n\r\nto school.\r\n\r\na. Is \u2013 come \r\n\r\nb. Is \u2013 comes \r\n\r\nc. Am \u2013 comes \r\n\r\nd. Are \u2013 come \r\n\r\ne. Is \u2013 coming \r\n\r\n21. They.....grammar in englishshop right now.\r\n\r\na. are study d. is studying\r\n\r\nb. am studying e. was studying\r\n\r\nc. are studying\r\n\r\ntolong bantuin dong kk\u200b",
            "attachments": [],
            "answers": [
                {
                    "answer": "<p><strong>Jawaban:</strong></p><p>1. b. Germany</p><p>2. d. English</p><p><strong>Penjelasan:</strong></p><p>germany menyatakan negara</p><p>English menyatakan bahasa</p>",
                    "attachments": []
                }
            ]
        },
        {
            "slug": "russia-is-thecountry-in-the-world-655",
            "question": "Russia is the...country in the world",
            "attachments": [],
            "answers": [
                {
                    "answer": "<p><strong>Jawaban:</strong></p><p>largest</p><p><strong>Penjelasan:</strong></p><p>Rusia adalah negara terbesar di dunia</p><p></p><p></p><p>semoga membantu:)</p>",
                    "attachments": []
                }
            ]
        },
        {
            "slug": "jakarta-isthan-sidoarjo-179",
            "question": "Jakarta is....than sidoarjo",
            "attachments": [],
            "answers": [
                {
                    "answer": "<p><strong>Jawaban:</strong></p><p>big</p><p><strong>Penjelasan:</strong></p><p>artinya lebih besar</p><p></p>",
                    "attachments": []
                }
            ]
        },
        {
            "slug": "in-the-misty-moming-on-the-1-of-time-weve-lost-the-2-282",
            "question": "In the misty moming, on the ... (1) of time    We've lost the ... (2) sun, a final sign\r\nAs the misty moming ....(3) away to die\r\nReaching for the stars, we...(4) the sky\r\nWe.... (5) across the air before we learned to fly\r\nWe thought that it ... (6) never end\r\nWe'd glide above the ground before we learned to run, run\r\nNow it... (7) our world has come undone\r\nOh they ... (8) that it's over\r\n(9) had to be\r\n(10) children of the sea, oh\r\nAnd it\r\nWe're ...\u200b",
            "attachments": [],
            "answers": [
                {
                    "answer": "<p><strong>Jawaban:</strong></p><p>gue mistery shop.......... </p>",
                    "attachments": []
                },
                {
                    "answer": "<p><strong>Jawaban:</strong></p><p>Maksudnyagimana ya kak</p>",
                    "attachments": []
                }
            ]
        },
        {
            "slug": "if-i-had-enough-money-a-i-will-go-on-safari-102",
            "question": "If I had enough money, ..................    a.\r\n\r\nI will go on Safari to Kenya.\r\n\r\nb.\r\n\r\nI would go on Safari to Kenya.\r\n\r\nc.\r\n\r\nI can go on Safari to Kenya.\r\n\r\nd.\r\n\r\nI shall go on Safari to Kenya.\r\n\r\nIf I had enough money, ..................\r\n\r\n\r\na.\r\nI will go on Safari to Kenya.\r\n\r\n\r\nb.\r\nI would go on Safari to Kenya.\r\n\r\n\r\nc.\r\nI can go on Safari to Kenya.\r\n\r\n\r\nd.\r\nI shall go on Safari to Kenya.\u200b",
            "attachments": [],
            "answers": [
                {
                    "answer": "<p><strong>Jawaban:</strong></p><p>A. I will go on safari to kenya</p>",
                    "attachments": []
                },
                {
                    "answer": "<p><strong>Jawaban:</strong></p><p>b   I would go on Safari to Kenya</p><p><strong>Penjelasan:</strong></p><p> semoga membantu, maaf jika salah</p><p></p>",
                    "attachments": []
                }
            ]
        },
        {
            "slug": "6-the-most-distinguishing-characteristic-of-an-elephant-is-364",
            "question": "6. The most distinguishing characteristic of an    elephant is.....\r\n(A). its clumsiness\r\n(B). its thick legs\r\n(C). its large body\r\n(D). its long nose \r\n\r\nartinya....\u200b",
            "attachments": [],
            "answers": [
                {
                    "answer": "<p><strong>Jawaban:</strong></p><p>D. Its long nose</p><p><strong>Penjelasan:</strong></p><p>Yang paling membedakan dari karakteristik gajah adalah D. hidungnya yang panjang :)</p>",
                    "attachments": []
                }
            ]
        },
        {
            "slug": "bahasan-inggris-nya-kamu-sedang-apa-sekarang-131",
            "question": "Bahasan Inggris nya kamu sedang apa sekarang\u200b",
            "attachments": [],
            "answers": [
                {
                    "answer": "<p>What are you doing now?</p>",
                    "attachments": []
                },
                {
                    "answer": "<p><strong>Jawaban:</strong></p><p>What Are You Doing? </p><p><strong>Penjelasan:</strong></p><p>Utu lah Arti nya jika translate kedalam bhsa Inggris Kawan</p><p>maaf jika salah</p>",
                    "attachments": []
                }
            ]
        },
        {
            "slug": "12-they-will-be-here-soon-the-word-they-refers-to-a-nabil-385",
            "question": "12. They will be here soon. The word they refers to ....    A. Nabil and Jaka\r\nB. Jaka and Mrs. Maya\r\nC. Jaka and Gita\r\nD. Erigo and Gita\u200b",
            "attachments": [],
            "answers": [
                {
                    "answer": "<p><strong>Jawaban:</strong></p><p>C Jaka dan Gita</p><p><strong>Penjelasan:</strong></p><p>maaf kalau salah </p>",
                    "attachments": []
                }
            ]
        }
    ]
}